# Ufuk UYSAL

## Front End Web Developer

in LinkedIn 🕏 Portfolio 🜎 Github 🕦 Youtube 🖂 ufuk.uysI5@gmail.com 📞 +32 0487 63 78 42

Dedicated, passionate, highly skilled and self-motivated individual, with hands on coding experience, looking forward to new opportunities in web page and application development.

## **Professional Experience**

11/2020 - present **High Stone,** Front End Developer

• I'm helping develop it using Next Js in a project called Hyrai. We are trying to achieve maximum efficiency by using the Scrum methodology. Thanks to experienced developers, I find the opportunity to learn continuously.

08/2015 - 02/2019 Turkish Land Forces Command, Military Officier (Lieutenant)

• Trained for IT and programming in C++

• Worked with software developers on radar-related applications

• Led and commanded large team, both in academy and in field.

## **Education and Training**

08/2020 - present Intec Brussel, Front End Developer

08/2020 - 09/2020 Open Summer of Code, Front End Web Developer

09/2019 - 04/2020 https://hackyourfuture.be/, Web Development-Front End Web Developer

09/2011 – 08/2015 Turkish Military Academy, Ankara (Turkey), Bachelor Degree - Electronic Engineering

## Certificates

- Certificate HackYourFuture-Belgium (Full-Time) Front End Development Program ☑
- Certificate FreeCodeCamp JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures ☑
- Certificate FreeCodeCamp Responsive Web Design ☑

#### **Technical Skills**

#### Front End

- HTML5
- CSS3, Tailwind CSS, Bootstrap 4, Material UI
- Saas, jQuery
- · Vanilla JS, ES6, TypeScript
- · GulpJs, Webpack
- ReactjS, Redux, Next Js, React Native

#### **Version Control**

- Git
- GitKraken

#### **Deployments**

- Heroku
- Netlify
- Vercel

## **Design Tools**

- Figma
- Sketch

#### Back-end

- · Node.js, NPM, Yarn
- Express

## **Development Methodologies**

- Scrum
- Agile
- Waterfall

## **Operating System**

- Linux
- Microsoft

#### Data

- SQL Server
- MySQL
- MongoDB
- Firebase

#### **Communication Platforms**

- Slack
- Microsoft Teams
- Discord

#### **Test Tools**

- MochaJs
- Jest

#### **Skills**

## Organisational / Managerial Skills

- Military Background: Having 4 years of work experience as an officer
- Team Leadership: Managed teams of 30-200 men.
- High Stamina: Used to work under urgent deadline schedules
- Flexibility-Fast and Lifelong Learner
- · Motivated and Self-driven person
- Strategic Thinking-Problem solving
- · Working in a team or individual

#### **Communication Skills**

- Excellent communication skills gained through years of experience in the military, as well as civilian sectors;
- Active listening
- Confidence
- · Giving and receiving feedback
- Volume and clarity
- · Open-minded
- Responsiveness

#### Languages

English (B2-C1), Dutch (B1), Turkish (Native)

#### Interests

Playing Soccer, Volleyball, Follow Science, Sci-fi and fantasy movies, Technology news, articles, Table Tennis

## References

**Benedikt Lantsoght**, *Instructor*, Intec Brussel Benedikt.Lantsoght@intec.be, 0499388227

## **Additional Information**

- Immediately available
- Eligible for individual vocational training (**IBO**). This is an advantageous formula: you teach me the tricks of the trade and do not pay any wages or social security during my training. More info : https://www.vdab.be/ibo ☑